Emerging from the curve of the bridge, the sky’s blue slipped between the clouds
Because of how hot it has recently been, I’ve been waiting for the wind to blow past me
As I’m sitting in the shade of a tree
Something lands on my cheek
And as I look overhead, I see above me the blossoms chip off
Akin to gently falling flowers, we forgot how to breathe ¹
Even blinking is such a pain
You know yourself that even today will turn to past the next day
I’m just waiting for the wind to come
And so as we forgot how to utter all words
Even telling goodbye’s such a pain
Just the image of flowers falling on a sunny day
Makes it look like it’s spring’s take on a snow storm
Meeting with you on the next day
I see that not so many people are here viewing flowers
The spring’s scent is leaving the air
I wonder if this year as well summer will reach us
Emerging from the curve of the bridge, your face peeked from the end of the road
I wonder how much there is left
How many more times will we be able to meet in this spring
On a riverside hill, I sit in the shade of a tree
Surrounded by blossoms, not different from yesterday
Completely forgetting how to breathe in the air
Even blinking for us's such a pain
Right now this vile storm is taking all the blossoms in
Just like a spring thief
And all our time today has gone away with the wind
Even standing is such a pain
In the gaps between the blossoms, the sky's chipping off
Spring’s snow storm still rages on
Today again I’m going to see you
Sitting in the shade of a tree
A single sigh takes the stage
The blossoms are no more
Tomorrow again I’m about to see you
The spring is nearing its end
The falling time stays here in remnants of what we used to be
When singing of love, there are never enough words
Even rhyming them's a pain
Can you even begin to describe the moment flowers start to bloom with such a thing?
Akin to gently falling flowers, forgetting how to let out a voice
Even blinking for us's such a pain
Only we are here to watch the cherry blossoms
Don’t chip them off just yet, spring’s snow storm
There’s only that much left
So little, that you can count them down
Only two blossoms left
Just one blossom left
And now only leaves are up there, chipping off
The spring has now met its end