It's alright, it's alright
If you sleep it over, everything will straighten out one way or another
What's the matter, why make that face?
It doesn't really make a difference either way
In vain I'm waiting for love in front of a train station
I have nothing else to do after all
Please explain to me the worth of dishonesty
Don't say a word, forget about such things as love
Tell me about everything, even what brings you pain
If just one such dragonfly is enough, I would rather forget
I can't listen to you spewing nothing but empty words
Yet I don't want to say it
It's alright, no matter how much you try to express yourself
Words are never enough for you
What's the matter, don't you get it?
- This anguish
In vain I'm waiting for love at your front door
Trying to suppress my voice, I struggle for air
Please teach me the meaning of regret
If you can, please forget things like that heat haze and the events of today
And please sing nothing but songs of simple sorrowful love
I would rather you not say "For the finale, a single kiss is enough"
I can't forget even your empty words
I don't want to know the truth
Someday you'll forget such things as that heat haze and the events of today, right? It hurts
If that one hesitation is love, then I would rather be ignorant
Let me hear even your empty words more and more
Don't say a word, forget about such things as tomorrow
No matter how many times, please tell me about even what brings you pain
A single unsightly dragonfly is plenty, I want it so bad - I could be absorbed by it
Let me hear even your empty words more and more
I just want your love