I know I'm a liar, I admit it
still, still Elma it hurts
even though it's time to say goodbye
I'll sing until the darkening night arrives
Me and Elma, in the morning sunlight shining through the trees
are you still sleepy?
as the early summer begins, we approach the forest of May
Walking with the dew from the flowers on our faces
see, they're like tear drops
Let's yawn like this
if you want we can even sit in a chair
There's nothing that can't be forgiven
you can become kinder
Like this, in some far away country
lying sprawled out in a shallow summer
without shedding tears or saying words
without simply knowing the deepness of the night
I know I'm a liar, I admit it
still, still Elma it hurts
even though it's time to say goodbye
I'll sing until the darkening night arrives
if you don't see difficult or painful things you won't understand them
with your eyes closed you ran away
walking a moonlit path
cramped rooms, cold nights
sleepy afternoons, lonely mornings
in the words of farewell, I'm looking at your face
Like this, in some far away country
lying sprawled out in a shallow summer
without shedding tears or saying words
simply looking at the blueness of the sky
simply not knowing of the ending between us
I know I'm a liar, I admit it
still, still Elma it hurts
even though it's time to say goodbye
I'll sing until the darkening night arrives