The moon that floated in the night like a jelly fish
Has split open
When I glance at someone’s back at the bus stop
You, as you were that summer, are in my head
Only
Torii gates, dried-out clouds;
the scent of summer strokes my cheek
Until I become an adult,
look,
I’ll keep standing on tiptoe to make myself taller
Tired out from playing,
behind the bus stop I could even see the sky
Even if the summer comes to an end soon
I’ll definitely, definitely remember
Becoming an adult without being able to catch up
Night blooms in your pocket
If I can’t put it into words I’ll be alone
But that’s all right,
I’ve already resigned myself to it
Only
A summer day, dried-out clouds,
Nanking cherry trees, a rusted stoplight
In my memories, it always smells like summer
Photographs are just scraps of paper
And memories are nothing but garbage
Because I didn’t understand that, I kept my mouth shut
In my memory, you rest forever on the single stone in a summer field*
Becoming an adult while looking down
I can’t catch up, it’s just a sunny day for you
Unable to put things into words, we climbed the hill
In our shadows,
night is blooming
We’ve become adults
while looking down
Clap your hands how you like
Climbing the road up the hill at sunset
Our shadows…
Becoming an adult without being able to catch up
Night blooms in your pocket
Even if we can’t put it into words, we are one**
That’s enough, I think
I’m only chewing over memories
of you