If there’s a heart inside my body,
right below my throat,
Then that must be where you are
I’ve known for a long time
That as I got older I would even forget your face
Because I want to know
the moment that words are able to form
inside my body,
in my throat
If the dawn comes like this…
I hope that my memories don’t dry out
I hope that I don’t lose this song
Don’t forget,
for just a little longer,
The lonely parade
I’ve thought for a long time that
Gods might reside in your fingertips
Since before today,
before yesterday,
since a long, long time past
I’ve known that
Inside my body,
right below my throat
Are the days when I’ve only been imitating your song
I hope that I don’t forget
The temperature of this moment in which you’re not here
With memories that I hope won’t dry out
With this song that I haven’t been able to forget
Just a little bit more,
for just a little longer
I’ll make a lonely parade