Words whitened to grey and have a color like cappuccino
Don't bother with excuses, leave them by the window
I can't count them all
Heart whitened to grey has a color like cappuccino
Don't bother with excuses, let's gulp down the cappuccino
And pretend to be foolish
As if reluctant, the rain flows
As we drown in the flowers storming us
These memories I keep so that you won't fade away
Please, please, please so you won't overflow
A shore waiting for waves in a crimson sunset
Reflecting on the windows
An august in Visby,
I waited in vain for the sea to roar with the breeze remaining
The whiteness of the flower that swam in summer, the night rain
Drowning in the flowing night
A flower that nobody can let fade
Please, please, please place it inside my chest
Something's been wrong for a long time
I just wanted to be told a way to live
I no longer have anything I can pay you back with
If you can't answer, just one word will do
I don't understand
I really don't understand
As if reluctant, the rain flows
As we drown in the flowers storming us
The poem I'm writing so you won't fade
Please, please, please so I won't forget
Yet another summer comes to an end,
Keeping this one flower close to my chest with tears escaping from behind my eyelids
This poem, made so you won't fade away
Please, please so you won't overflow