In a rain-drenched playground,
I remembered yesterday’s fireworks,
Your distracted face from that time,
and the scent of summer still on the wind.
Fall comes,
winter comes,
After we finished
our long slumber
Riding the clouds,
riding the wind,
Let’s go far away,
there’s nothing for us here.
In a playground where flowers fluttered,
I remembered yesterday’s sunset,
Your cold, transparent self from that time,
and summer still lingering on your cheeks.
Spring comes,
summer comes,
When we awakened
from our deep slumber
Becoming water,
becoming flowers
Let’s gaze at the sky,
we don’t need anything like words.
There’s no such thing as gods,
And realizing our dreams is a lie,
So let’s put a stop to work and school.
If it’s natural to forget things,
Don't create words for these memories
Let’s seal our mouths so we don’t forget.
I’ll wait for you,
as summer passes,
Someday, when
we can see the end
Riding the clouds,
riding the wind
Like we’re sleeping,
just…
Fall comes,
winter comes,
After we finished
our long slumber
Riding the clouds,
riding the wind,
Let’s go far away,
There’s nothing for us here.
I want to live with you alone.