Say it
You see,
I actually realized already
Look, about that thing you said
I didn't feel like
Thinking about it too much
So I had forgotten about it, but
Living blindly, recklessly, delusionly
Impulsively, impatiently, negatively didn’t do me any good​
I’m sure​
That on the last day of my life, when I think of what’s gone before​
All of it, all of it will be unspeakably precious, but​
Ah,
On that last day of my life, you won’t be there
More, more, more​
Say that more clearly​
You see,
I’m not sure how to tell you
That the sky is blue
Or what
I’d have to do to make you understand
That the clouds at night are high
Say it
You see,
I actually know
That you’re already gone
You see
You'll probably just call me obstinate
And I want to forget, but
Say it more clearly
Make a note so you won't forget it
Let's meet tomorrow at ten on the train platform, or something like that
Even if its petals scatter, a peony is still a flower
Even if summer ends, the memories of it are still cherished
Put it into words, give voice to it
Say it
And then if I could see you on the last day of my life
I'm sure,
Even on the last day of my life, that I'd sing of love
Because you'd tell me none of it, none of it was in vain
Ah,
I still can't believe that on the last day of my life,
You won't be here
More, more, more, more
More, more, more, you have to
Please,
Say it,
More clearly