When the alarm clock rang,
I finally woke up
The flu I had yesterday doesn’t seem real anymore
I think of going out, but, ah, the forecast says it looks like rain
Well, I couldn’t go anyway
because it’s still dark
A dry throat,
a hurting heart–
all these human thing
are getting in my way
Lift your head at the speed of the farewell
Someday dawn will finally break
Come on, try and open your eyes
Because I’ve pictured your sleepy eyes so many times
I finally decided to take an umbrella and go out anyway,
which was good, but
I think I might’ve thrown away my shoes
And it’s not like I’ve got the courage to go barefoot so…
I guess I don’t really care?
What do I want to do?
What should I do for dinner?
If the rain lets up, I’ll go out
Even though I don’t really want to see people
At this speed I swim through today,
And if my hand finally touches you…
Come on, try and open your eyes
Because I remember you and your sleepy eyes,
even though I’ve forgotten them
There you are by the hill,
laughing, “It’s been so long, hasn’t it?”
as you bring your face close to mine
“Let’s go together,” you say
Under a barn in Lapland
On the old streets of Gamlastan
The summer grass is getting in my way
At this speed I swim through today,
And if my hand finally touches you…
Come on, open your eyes
And see that I’ve forgotten you
Lift your head at the speed of the farewell
Someday dawn will finally break...
Come on, open your eyes
And see that I’ve drawn pictures of your sleepy eyes so many times