The scenery doesn’t change; on a faded afternoon
I’m lying in the deep indigo beneath the overpass
I hear a single clap for my blank-page life
I was singing about my own emptiness today, as usual
So things wouldn’t change,
I wrote a story starring you in my notebook
My gas and water being cut off, society, and the news are all someone else’s problem
Look, my life is like ink
The dream I had when I was young gets closer to its expiration date as I get older
Though I just, I just look up at the clouds
As usual, they flow through my field of vision
In the distant night sky I looked up at, flowers swam
So many that it could be mistaken for spring
As if I’d just lost sight of you
I looked down so I wouldn’t trip
Life is made of nothing but compromises
I don’t believe in hearts or fate or love songs or life
After all, if you can’t sell something it has no value
I intentionally discarded the present I dreamed of, and now I’m lying here waiting for its expiration date
Behind my eyelids, I just, I just saw
An imagined, distant vision of you
In my notebook, flowers swim in the corner of a faded night
One more is in my eye
Life is just one compromise after another
I learned that pretty fast
Elma, it’s you
You alone are my music
There are only eighty more characters in this song
Because maybe the only value of a life is in the way it ends
I just, I just picture you
As even the indigo filling my vision is blurred
In the distant sky I looked up at, flowers swam
Deep indigo covers my eyes
It’s just, it’s just…
In the distant sky I looked up at, you are cooling off
As if you were just swimming in the night
I’ve thought about it, but I still don’t understand
Under the blue sky, I waited for you
On that breezy afternoon, my imagination escaped the confines of the day
Hey, where do I go from here?
No one has told me how to proceed
I looked into your eyes and without a word I walked away
I’ve thought about it, but I still don’t understand
Youth is so boring
I tried to give up piano, but I can’t break the habit of playing on my desk*
Hey, what will I do in the future?
It shouldn’t be music, right?
Don’t worry
Even if I plucked a single string in my heart
No matter what I did, it wouldn’t disappear, even now, so
Hey, I still remember
I’m mistaken
I don’t understand, I don’t care
About all you humans or the truth or love or the world or pain or life
Wanting to know what’s right or wrong is just a self-preservation instinct
It’s your fault that I thought that
I’ve thought about it, but I still don’t understand why I truly don’t want to get older
Just thinking “Someday I’m going to die” makes my chest feel hollow
“What will I do in the future?”
When I grew up I understood That I’m not going to do anything at all
How do I explain why I hate people who put on happy faces?
It’s an inferiority complex haunting my unsatisfied mind like a ghost
I’m not mistaken
Hey, with all your differences, you all are human
When you don’t have love or salvation or kindness or a foundation, it feels bad
Feeling pain at something like a love song is a self-preservation instinct
Do I really not care? It’s your fault
I’ve thought about it, but I still don’t understand
Why just living is painful
Why you can’t make a living from something like music
I don’t care if the lyrics or whatever are lazily done
I don’t care about anything
I’m probably not mistaken
I’m sure I’m not mistaken
I’m mistaken, I understand
I don’t care
About all you humans or the truth or love or salvation or kindness or life
Not being able to give the right answer is a self-preservation instinct
I don’t care, it’s your fault
Even I had faith in something once
Now the feeling is nothing but garbage
I wrote to you so many times
I didn’t care about whether I’d be rich and famous
It’s true,
it’s really true,
that’s how it was back then
That’s why I
That’s why I gave up on music
Words whitened to grey and have a color like cappuccino
Don't bother with excuses, leave them by the window
I can't count them all
Heart whitened to grey has a color like cappuccino
Don't bother with excuses, let's gulp down the cappuccino
And pretend to be foolish
As if reluctant, the rain flows
As we drown in the flowers storming us
These memories I keep so that you won't fade away
Please, please, please so you won't overflow
A shore waiting for waves in a crimson sunset
Reflecting on the windows
An august in Visby,
I waited in vain for the sea to roar with the breeze remaining
The whiteness of the flower that swam in summer, the night rain
Drowning in the flowing night
A flower that nobody can let fade
Please, please, please place it inside my chest
Something's been wrong for a long time
I just wanted to be told a way to live
I no longer have anything I can pay you back with
If you can't answer, just one word will do
I don't understand
I really don't understand
As we drown in the flowers storming us
The poem I'm writing so you won't fade
Please, please, please so I won't forget
Yet another summer comes to an end,
Keeping this one flower close to my chest with tears escaping from behind my eyelids
This poem, made so you won't fade away
Please, please so you won't overflow
If there’s a heart inside my body,
right below my throat,
Then that must be where you are
I’ve known for a long time
That as I got older I would even forget your face
Because I want to know
the moment that words are able to form
inside my body,
in my throat
If the dawn comes like this…
I hope that my memories don’t dry out
I hope that I don’t lose this song
Don’t forget,
for just a little longer,
The lonely parade
I’ve thought for a long time that
Gods might reside in your fingertips
Since before today,
before yesterday,
since a long, long time past
I’ve known that
Inside my body,
right below my throat
Are the days when I’ve only been imitating your song
I hope that I don’t forget
The temperature of this moment in which you’re not here
With memories that I hope won’t dry out
With this song that I haven’t been able to forget
Just a little bit more,
for just a little longer
I’ll make a lonely parade
Say it
You see,
I actually realized already
Look, about that thing you said
I didn't feel like
Thinking about it too much
So I had forgotten about it, but
Living blindly, recklessly, delusionly
Impulsively, impatiently, negatively didn’t do me any good​
I’m sure​
That on the last day of my life, when I think of what’s gone before​
All of it, all of it will be unspeakably precious, but​
Ah,
On that last day of my life, you won’t be there
More, more, more​
Say that more clearly​
You see,
I’m not sure how to tell you
That the sky is blue
Or what
I’d have to do to make you understand
That the clouds at night are high
Say it
You see,
I actually know
That you’re already gone
You see
You'll probably just call me obstinate
And I want to forget, but
Say it more clearly
Make a note so you won't forget it
Let's meet tomorrow at ten on the train platform, or something like that
Even if its petals scatter, a peony is still a flower
Even if summer ends, the memories of it are still cherished
Put it into words, give voice to it
Say it
And then if I could see you on the last day of my life
I'm sure,
Even on the last day of my life, that I'd sing of love
Because you'd tell me none of it, none of it was in vain
Ah,
I still can't believe that on the last day of my life,
You won't be here
More, more, more, more
More, more, more, you have to
Please,
Say it,
More clearly