I’ve thought about it, but I still don’t understand
Under the blue sky, I waited for you
On that breezy afternoon, my imagination escaped the confines of the day
Hey, where do I go from here?
No one has told me how to proceed
I looked into your eyes and without a word I walked away
I’ve thought about it, but I still don’t understand
Youth is so boring
I tried to give up piano, but I can’t break the habit of playing on my desk*
Hey, what will I do in the future?
It shouldn’t be music, right?
Don’t worry
Even if I plucked a single string in my heart
No matter what I did, it wouldn’t disappear, even now, so
Hey, I still remember
I’m mistaken
I don’t understand, I don’t care
About all you humans or the truth or love or the world or pain or life
Wanting to know what’s right or wrong is just a self-preservation instinct
It’s your fault that I thought that
I’ve thought about it, but I still don’t understand why I truly don’t want to get older
Just thinking “Someday I’m going to die” makes my chest feel hollow
“What will I do in the future?”
When I grew up I understood That I’m not going to do anything at all
How do I explain why I hate people who put on happy faces?
It’s an inferiority complex haunting my unsatisfied mind like a ghost
I’m not mistaken
Hey, with all your differences, you all are human
When you don’t have love or salvation or kindness or a foundation, it feels bad
Feeling pain at something like a love song is a self-preservation instinct
Do I really not care? It’s your fault
I’ve thought about it, but I still don’t understand
Why just living is painful
Why you can’t make a living from something like music
I don’t care if the lyrics or whatever are lazily done
I don’t care about anything
I’m probably not mistaken
I’m sure I’m not mistaken
I’m mistaken, I understand
I don’t care
About all you humans or the truth or love or salvation or kindness or life
Not being able to give the right answer is a self-preservation instinct
I don’t care, it’s your fault
Even I had faith in something once
Now the feeling is nothing but garbage
I wrote to you so many times
I didn’t care about whether I’d be rich and famous
It’s true,
it’s really true,
that’s how it was back then
That’s why I
That’s why I gave up on music