The scenery doesn’t change; on a faded afternoon
I’m lying in the deep indigo beneath the overpass
I hear a single clap for my blank-page life
I was singing about my own emptiness today, as usual
So things wouldn’t change,
I wrote a story starring you in my notebook
My gas and water being cut off, society, and the news are all someone else’s problem
Look, my life is like ink
The dream I had when I was young gets closer to its expiration date as I get older
Though I just, I just look up at the clouds
As usual, they flow through my field of vision
In the distant night sky I looked up at, flowers swam
So many that it could be mistaken for spring
As if I’d just lost sight of you
I looked down so I wouldn’t trip
Life is made of nothing but compromises
I don’t believe in hearts or fate or love songs or life
After all, if you can’t sell something it has no value
I intentionally discarded the present I dreamed of, and now I’m lying here waiting for its expiration date
Behind my eyelids, I just, I just saw
An imagined, distant vision of you
In my notebook, flowers swim in the corner of a faded night
One more is in my eye
Life is just one compromise after another
I learned that pretty fast
Elma, it’s you
You alone are my music
There are only eighty more characters in this song
Because maybe the only value of a life is in the way it ends
I just, I just picture you
As even the indigo filling my vision is blurred
In the distant sky I looked up at, flowers swam
Deep indigo covers my eyes
It’s just, it’s just…
In the distant sky I looked up at, you are cooling off
As if you were just swimming in the night
I’ve thought about it, but I still don’t understand
Under the blue sky, I waited for you
On that breezy afternoon, my imagination escaped the confines of the day
Hey, where do I go from here?
No one has told me how to proceed
I looked into your eyes and without a word I walked away
I’ve thought about it, but I still don’t understand
Youth is so boring
I tried to give up piano, but I can’t break the habit of playing on my desk*
Hey, what will I do in the future?
It shouldn’t be music, right?
Don’t worry
Even if I plucked a single string in my heart
No matter what I did, it wouldn’t disappear, even now, so
Hey, I still remember
I’m mistaken
I don’t understand, I don’t care
About all you humans or the truth or love or the world or pain or life
Wanting to know what’s right or wrong is just a self-preservation instinct
It’s your fault that I thought that
I’ve thought about it, but I still don’t understand why I truly don’t want to get older
Just thinking “Someday I’m going to die” makes my chest feel hollow
“What will I do in the future?”
When I grew up I understood That I’m not going to do anything at all
How do I explain why I hate people who put on happy faces?
It’s an inferiority complex haunting my unsatisfied mind like a ghost
I’m not mistaken
Hey, with all your differences, you all are human
When you don’t have love or salvation or kindness or a foundation, it feels bad
Feeling pain at something like a love song is a self-preservation instinct
Do I really not care? It’s your fault
I’ve thought about it, but I still don’t understand
Why just living is painful
Why you can’t make a living from something like music
I don’t care if the lyrics or whatever are lazily done
I don’t care about anything
I’m probably not mistaken
I’m sure I’m not mistaken
I’m mistaken, I understand
I don’t care
About all you humans or the truth or love or salvation or kindness or life
Not being able to give the right answer is a self-preservation instinct
I don’t care, it’s your fault
Even I had faith in something once
Now the feeling is nothing but garbage
I wrote to you so many times
I didn’t care about whether I’d be rich and famous
It’s true,
it’s really true,
that’s how it was back then
That’s why I
That’s why I gave up on music