The scenery doesn’t change; on a faded afternoon
I’m lying in the deep indigo beneath the overpass
I hear a single clap for my blank-page life
I was singing about my own emptiness today, as usual
So things wouldn’t change,
I wrote a story starring you in my notebook
My gas and water being cut off, society, and the news are all someone else’s problem
Look, my life is like ink
The dream I had when I was young gets closer to its expiration date as I get older
Though I just, I just look up at the clouds
As usual, they flow through my field of vision
In the distant night sky I looked up at, flowers swam
So many that it could be mistaken for spring
As if I’d just lost sight of you
I looked down so I wouldn’t trip
Life is made of nothing but compromises
I don’t believe in hearts or fate or love songs or life
After all, if you can’t sell something it has no value
I intentionally discarded the present I dreamed of, and now I’m lying here waiting for its expiration date
Behind my eyelids, I just, I just saw
An imagined, distant vision of you
In my notebook, flowers swim in the corner of a faded night
One more is in my eye
Life is just one compromise after another
I learned that pretty fast
Elma, it’s you
You alone are my music
There are only eighty more characters in this song
Because maybe the only value of a life is in the way it ends
I just, I just picture you
As even the indigo filling my vision is blurred
In the distant sky I looked up at, flowers swam
Deep indigo covers my eyes
It’s just, it’s just…
In the distant sky I looked up at, you are cooling off
As if you were just swimming in the night